<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Citations>
<RelevantCitations>
<Citation>
<PMID>16191490</PMID>
<Title>Effect of sibutramine on blood pressure in patients with obesity and well-controlled hypertension or normotension.</Title>
</Citation>
</RelevantCitations>
<NonrelevantCitations>
<Citation>
<PMID>16099715</PMID>
<Title>Sibutramine does not worsen sleep apnea syndrome: a randomized double-blind placebo-controlled study.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16128165</PMID>
<Title>[Obesity and metabolic syndrome: clinical and therapeutic review]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16135277</PMID>
<Title>Obesity.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16140592</PMID>
<Title>Rapid treatment of posttraumatic stress disorder with sibutramine.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16144896</PMID>
<Title>Anorectics on trial: a half century of federal regulation of prescription appetite suppressants.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16150386</PMID>
<Title>Childhood obesity. Treatment options.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16184258</PMID>
<Title>[Evaluation of the sibutramine effect on satiety with a visual analogue scale in obese adolescents]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16202254</PMID>
<Title>[Effects of sibutramine on blood glucose and lipids, body fat mass and insulin resistance in obese patients: a multi-center clinical trial]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16265126</PMID>
<Title>Drug Insight: appetite suppressants.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16309097</PMID>
<Title>[Acupuncture for treatment of simple obesity and its effect on serum leptin level of the patient]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16309105</PMID>
<Title>[Effect of electroacupuncture on metabolism of lipids in rats of obesity induced by sodium glutamate]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16385755</PMID>
<Title>New drug policy in childhood obesity.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16454448</PMID>
<Title>[The influence of body mass reduction on metabolic disorders and complications in patient with morbid obesity. Three years observation]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16463587</PMID>
<Title>Our experience with antidepressant treatment in the obese and type 2 diabetics.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16473261</PMID>
<Title>Pharmacotherapy to reduce visceral fat.</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16696212</PMID>
<Title>[The "problem obesity": viewpoint of the internist]</Title>
</Citation>
<Citation>
<PMID>16925226</PMID>
<Title>Diets, drugs, exercise, and behavioral modification: Where these work and where they do not.</Title>
</Citation>
</NonrelevantCitations>
</Citations>

